A Guide to the Kilby family Papers, 1665-1947
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Papers, 1665-1947
Library of Virginia
26674
4.05 cubic feet
Kilby family
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. Mildred K. Kilby, 1 March 1967.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Kilby family were prominent residents of Hanover and Nansemond Counties, Virginia. John Kilby (1758-1826) of Maryland married Elizabeth Thompson (1763-1818) on 25 December 1787 in Hanover County, Virginia. They had six children: John Thompson (1789-1838), Turpin (1792-1793), Turpin (1794-1832), Harriet (1797-1865), Spotswood (1800-1818), and Thomas Jefferson Kilby (1803-1881). John Thompson Kilby married Ann Newton (Jones) Baker (1800-1857), daughter of Matthias Jones and Mary (Riddick) Jones, and widow of Joseph B. Baker, at Suffolk, Virginia, on 1 May 1817. Harriet Kilby married Samuel Corbell on 4 May 1838 in Nansemond County, Virginia, and John L. Collins of Louisa County, Virginia, on 20 May 1855. Thomas Jefferson Kilby married Ann Upshur Smith (1803-1879) and Turpin Kilby married Martha Glazebrook (1796-1878) on 6 March 1817.
John Richardson Kilby (1819-1878), second of the seven children of Turpin (1794-1832) and Martha (Glazebrook) Kilby (1796-1878), was born in Hanover County, Virginia. He served as sheriff of Nansemond County, lawyer, member of the Virginia Convention, 1861, and served in the Virginia House of Delegates, 1849-1852. He married Martha Jane Louisa (1816-1888), daughter of Arthur (1779-1849) and Susan (Richardson) Smith (1781-), on 5 December 1838. Arthur Smith (1779-1849) operated a general store in Suffolk, Virginia, and served as postmaster of Suffolk, from 1804-1845. They had eight children, Walter, Leroy Richardson (1841- 1883), Wallace (1843-1899), Susan (1845-1917), Arthur Turpin (1847-1851), Wilbur J. Kilby (1850-1907), Livingston Clay (1852-1917), and Annette Maria (1853-1882).
Wilbur John Kilby (1850-1907), sixth of the eight children of John Richardson and Martha Jane Louisa Kilby, was educated at Randolph Macon College and University of Virginia. He was a lawyer in Suffolk, Virginia, and judge of the County Court of Nansemond, Virginia. He was also examiner of records in the second judicial circuit and the superintendent of Cedar Hill Cemetery in Nansemond County. He married Harriett Lanetta Brownley (1855-1887), daughter of Mary (1818-1881) and Joseph (d. 1878) Brownley of King and Queen County, Virginia, on 5 September 1876. They had four children: Miriam (1879-), Bradford (1876-), John Richardson, and Hilah Kilby. On 23 January 1889 Wilbur Kilby married Mary D.H. Finney (1850-1917).
Scope and Content Information
The Kilby family papers, 1665-1947, are organized into 4 series: Kilby family Papers, John R. Kilby Papers, Wilbur J. Kilby Papers, and Arthur Smith Papers. The collection includes accounts, bills of sale, certificates, clippings, correspondence, deeds, estate accounts, genealogical notes, ledgers, marriage records, memoirs, military records, obituaries, plats, postmasters accounts, promissory notes, receipts, sheriff fee and tax books, slave records, surveys, and wills, documenting a prominent Nansemond County, Virginia family.
These papers are most notable because they contain many records relating to Nansemond County, a county for which many records are no longer extant. Included are numerous deeds, plats, surveys, and wills, 1665- 1931. (An individual listing of each deed and will can be found in Appendix A at the end of the finding aid.) Included are overseer of the poor records and account books of levies and fees collected by John R. Kilby, as sheriff of Nansemond County, from c. 1840-1870. Included are accounts of the post office of Nansemond County, 1804-1844, when Arthur Smith was postmaster of the county. Also included are many estate accounts of Nansemond County residents, found in the John R. Kilby series. There are also many slave records throughout the collection, which include names, birth and death dates. Of note are letters from Randal Kilby, a former slave of the Kilby family who had gained his freedom and resettled in Liberia. This correspondence may be found in Series I: Kilby family papers.
The collection also includes military records from the 59th Virginia Militia, 1812, and the 16th Virginia Infantry, Confederate States of America. A memoir written by John Kilby describes his experiences in the Revolutionary war and his work with John Paul Jones (1747-1792). Also included are numerous genealogical notes and obituaries on the Blackwell, Glazebrook, Kilby, Riddick, Smith, and Thompson families of Hanover and Nansemond County and Norfolk, Virginia.
Appendixes A and B are not available online. A copy of the appendixes may be requested from the library.
Arrangement
Organized into 4 series: I. Kilby family papers, II. John R. Kilby papers, III. Wilbur J. Kilby papers, and IV. Arthur Smith papers.
Contents List
- Series I: Kilby family Papers 1665-1947
  The Kilby family papers are arranged alphabetically by folder title in four boxes and six oversize folders (see oversize folders 1-6). This series consists of accounts, clippings, correspondence, deeds, genealogical notes, notebooks, obituaries, plats and surveys, promissory notes, receipts, suit papers, and wills.
  Included are slave records, 1833-1854, containing receipts for the hire of slaves and a list of Washington, Henning, and Sarah Smith's slaves, 1853-1854; a notebook listing the members of the Suffolk Committee of Native Americans, 1855; and genealogical notes and obituaries from the Blackwell, Glazebrook, Kilby, Riddick, Smith, and Thompson families of Hanover and Nansemond County, Virginia. Within the genealogical notes are included letters to Bradford and Wilbur Kilby, 1890-1943, from family members researching their genealogy. Included are oaths and summonses from Nansemond County, 1820-1872; suit papers relating to the land of "Cross Swamp" in Nansemond County, 1835-1870; and suit papers of Wells administrators vs. Norfolk & Western Railway, 1899-1902; copies of general orders issued from the Adjutant and Inspector General's office, Richmond, Virginia, 1863-1864, from newspapers; and clippings and notes related to the history of Nansemond County, Virginia, 1893-1931.
  Within this series are the papers of some individual members of the Kilby family, such as Bradford Kilby, John Kilby, Leroy Kilby, and Josiah Riddick. The Bradford Kilby papers include correspondence, certificates from Randolph Macon College, and ration books. Of note within his papers are the record items of Suffolk Council, 1883-1907, compiled by Simon M. Lawrence, clerk of the Suffolk Council. This record is a compiled list of items presented to the Suffolk Council in the period 1883-1907, such as names of councilmen who served in Suffolk, when lights were introduced in the city, census statistics, what efforts were made for the poor, and the pavement of streets. The John Kilby papers included memoirs of the Revolutionary war and military career of John Paul Jones (1747-1792), written by John Kilby in September 1810. The Leroy R. Kilby papers include reports, returns, and muster rolls of the 16th Virginia Infantry, Company B, Confederate States of America, commanded by Captain Leroy R. Kilby. The Josiah Riddick papers, 1813-1814, contain muster rolls for the 59th Virginia Militia and a list of officers belonging to the 2nd regiment in the War of 1812. The Cowper family papers, 1842-1896, including accounts, correspondence, and receipts. Of note is a letter, 27 May 1861, to Fannie Cowper, Suffolk, Virginia, from a cousin in North Carolina, discussing the beginnings of the Civil War and sentiments in the South.
  Of note within the collection are the deeds, plats and surveys, and wills, 1665-1931, mainly from Nansemond County and Norfolk, Virginia. Many of the records pre-1866 of Nansemond County were burned, so these records provide information that is no longer extant. Deeds, patents, and wills exist for the: Allmond, Arnold, Bennett, Benton, Bernard, Boykin, Brewer, Brock, Brown, Butler, Campbell, Capps, Causey, Charlton, Cohoon, Colvin, Cowper, Crittenden, Crocker, Crump, Crumples, Cuddeback, Cutchin, Darden, Daughtrey, Dean, Decormis, Dillard, Flynn, Fort, Frew, Galloway, Gardner, Gaskins, Golden, Gray, Gregory, Hall, Harrell, Hathaway, Hawes, Haywood, Heffington, Hinton, Holland, Holowell, Howell, Johnson, Jones, Jordan, Keeling, Kelly, Kilby, Laderberg, Latimer, Lee, Levett, Little, Lockhart, Mann, McAlister, McClenny, McGuire, Meade, Meriditt, Miles, Minton, Montgomery, Moss, Murdaugh, Murray, Newton, Norfleet, Northcott, Nurney, Oliver, Page, Phillips, Philhower, Pinner, Prentis, Pretlow, Pruden, Pulling, Rawls, Reber, Reid, Riddick, Rogers, Saunders, Savage, Smith, Steel, Swepson, Swett, Tarlington, Tucker, Vaughan, Vickers, Walker, Webb, White, Whitehead, Whitley, Whittock, Williams, Williamson, Willis, Wise, Wood, Wright, and Young families and the Dismal Swamp Company. Also included are land patents, 1711-1805, to the Campbell, Fort, Jones, Lockhart, Meade, Murdaugh, O'sheal, Pulling, and Riddick families, land in Nansemond and Norfolk Counties, Virginia.
  Also included is a ledger containing a register of students, 1870-1903, of Suffolk Female Institute (Suffolk, Va.). The register contains the names of students, residence, age, name of parents, and sometimes death date. The front of the ledger includes marriage records of some of the students, including brides and grooms names, place and date of wedding. These records were copied and cataloged separately as MBRC 62 (accession 40347). Included are correspondence, promissory notes, agreements, and receipts for the Florida Land Association, 1859-1869, a joint venture between James Evans, Robert Webb, Nathaniel Riddick, Richard Riddick, and John R. Kilby, to purchase land on the Caloosahatchee River near Ft. Myers, Florida. The papers contain correspondence regarding the purchase and farming of the land; license for the purchase of a ship, "Belle"; receipts for the hiring of slaves from Virginia to work in Florida; and a receipt for slaves kept at Charleston Work House. Of note is a letter to James Evans, 27 July 1861, regarding the outbreak of the Civil War and the effect the war would have on the land venture.
  The correspondence, 1801-1908, pertain to health, local and national politics, finances, and contain mostly family letters between Bradford Kilby, Eddie Kilby, Hilah Kilby, John R. Kilby, John S. Kilby, Joseph M. Kilby, Kate G. Kilby, L. Clay Kilby, Lucille Kilby, Martha Kilby, Randal Kilby, T. Spotswood Kilby, Thomas E. Kilby, Thomas J. Kilby, Wilbur J. Kilby, and William Turpin Kilby. Of note is a letter, 12 March 1801, from Archibald Richardson, to Josiah Riddick, regarding politics and the election of Thomas Jefferson as president; letter, 9 January 1846, from the mayors office in Baltimore, Maryland, to the mayor of Norfolk, Virginia, introducing Robert Rankin, a lawyer for Thomas Kiar, a free negro who was being held in a Norfolk jail; letter, 11 January 1849, regarding the sale of slaves in Suffolk, Virginia; letter, 23 August, 1860, regarding the farming of land for cotton and cattle in Florida; letter, 18 July 1871, regarding the pension of Andrew McAlister, for the War of 1812; letter, 23 August 1879, from Thomas Jefferson Kilby, recounting his father's, John Kilby, military service with John Paul Jones and the Revolutionary war; letter, 4 December 1879, regarding the death of John R. Kilby and a resolution passed by the board of directors of the Preacher's Relief Society (Norfolk, Va.); and letter, 10 March 1898, from Wilbur J. Kilby, on the history Quakers in of Nansemond County. Also of note are letters, 1855-1859, from Randal Kilby, a slave who had belonged to the Kilby family but had gained his freedom and resettled in Liberia, to John R. Kilby. His letters describes the voyage to Africa, impressions of the country, farming, and activities of other former slaves who had also resettled in Liberia.
  - Abstract of titles (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounts, 1875-1878 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Brookland School (Albemarle Co., Va.), 1858-1859 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Central Hotel property, 1871-1895 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, Adj. and Ins. general's office, C.S.A., General orders, 1863-1864 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, miscellaneous, 1875-1904 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1801-1858 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1860-1879 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1880-1908 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cowper family papers, 1842-1896 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Deeds, 1759-1822 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Deeds, 1825-1853 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Deeds, 1854-1872 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Deeds, 1873-1889 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Deeds, 1890-1931 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Florida Land Association, 1859-1869 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Genealogical notes (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Genealogical notes (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Genealogical notes, Correspondence regarding, 1890-1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Genealogical notes, History of the Glazebrook families (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bradford Kilby, Certificates, 1890-1897 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bradford Kilby, Correspondence, 1891-1905 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bradford Kilby, Correspondence, 1906-1947 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bradford Kilby, Correspondence, nd (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bradford Kilby, Papers, 1890-1907 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bradford Kilby, Record items of Suffolk County, 1883-1907 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - John Kilby, Memoirs, 1810 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - John R. Kilby, Jr., Certificates, 1895-1899 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Leroy R. Kilby, Papers, 1863-1876 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - T. Spotswood Kilby, Papers, 1842-1858 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Land patents, 1716-1767 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Andrew McAlister, Account book, 1836-1837 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1817-1941 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Notebooks, 1901 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Notebook, bounty claims not yet disclosed, 1852-1857 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Notes and clippings on Nansemond County (Va.) history, 1893-1931 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Obituaries, 1878-1906 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Plats and surveys, 1665-1908 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Plats and surveys, nd (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Promissory notes, 1842-1877 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 1871-1907 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Receipts, 1807-1900 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Record of bonds issued by Nansemond County (Va.), 1861 June (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Josiah Riddick, Jr., Military records, 1813-1814 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Slave records, 1833-1854 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Suffolk (Va.) Committee on Native Americans, 1855 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Suffolk Female Institute, 1885 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Suit papers, 1835-1903 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Suit papers, 1835-1903 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Suit papers, Oaths and summons, 1820-1872 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Virginia House Bills No. 158 and 188, 1869-1870 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Wills, 1674-1916 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Suffolk Female Institute, Register of students, 1870-1903 (Volume on shelf)
- Series II: John R. Kilby Papers, 1834-1904
  The John R. Kilby papers are arranged alphabetically by folder title in three boxes and fourteen volumes and divided into two subseries. Subseries have been designated for Papers; and Accounts books and ledgers. This series consists of accounts, bank books, bills of sale, broadsides, contracts, correspondence, estate accounts and records, ledgers, promissory notes, receipts, and county records, of John R. Kilby of Nansemond County, Virginia. The paper subseries relate mostly to Kilby's personal and professional life as a lawyer and member of the Virginia House of Delegates, 1849-1852. The account books and ledgers relate mainly to his career as sheriff of Nansemond County, c. 1840-1870.
  - Subseries 1: Papers, 1834-1887
    Included within this subseries are accounts and receipts, 1834-1877, for subscriptions, merchandise, taxes, doctors, clothing, tuition, attorney fees, and court fees. Of note are the bills of sale for slaves, 1840-1860. The bills often include the age or date of birth and first name of the slaves. The bills are also interesting because of a note written 22 January 1902 by Wilbur J. Kilby, in which he states the need to preserve the papers, in the case that the United States government reimburses the family for the prices of the slaves that were set free during the Civil War.
    The papers also include a broadside for the sale of the land of Joseph Bunch in Nansemond County, 1853; estate accounts with the family of Richard H. Riddick and W.B. Whitehead; military commission of the 59th Infantry regiment of the Virginia Militia, 1843; and stock certificates from the Suffolk Savings Bank, 1852-1859. The oaths include Kilby's oath as an attorney in Richmond, Virginia, 1855; amnesty oaths of Richard H. Riddick, James B. Norfleet, Elisha Norfleet, George W. Briggs, Robert R. Smith, Richard T. Riddick, Bartholomew Bowers, Henry L. Tynes, Samuel Eley, and John E. Humes, 1865; and a copy of the amnesty proclamation, 1865.
    Topics of the correspondence include numerous legal cases in Nansemond County, family, finances, health, estate accounts, and local, national, and internationals politics. Of note is a letter from W.L. Riddick, 2 December 1849, regarding the Whig party; letter, 27 January 1850, from John Bunch, on the subject of growing tensions between the North and South; letter, 17 May 1852, from Nathaniel Riddick, regarding Virginia politics; letter, 1853 October 22, from Washington Riddick on his travels through Europe and European politics; letter, 9 December 1854, from William Wright, regarding the hiring of slaves at Yates Free School in Norfolk, Virginia; and a letter, 29 January, 1857, from Harriet Collins, Kilby's aunt, and 23 December 1858, from B. Devany, regarding the sale of slaves; and letters dated 20 May 1868, 20 July 1868, and 1 December 1868, regarding Virginia politics after the Civil War.
    The correspondence, 1843-1930, includes letters from Robertson Arnold, W.G. Atkinson, Thomas H. Barnes, W.D. Barnes, Kader Biggs, E.T. Blamire, J.M. Blanton, William Briggs, Richard H. Browne, John Bunch, Arabella Bunkley, John J. Burroughs, Thomas A. Burton, John B. Cary, L.E. Casey, H.A. Claiborne, John C. Cohoon, Harriet Collins, John R. Copeland, J.D. Corbell, Samuel V. Corbell, Henry Craley, R.T. Daniel, John Davis Day, James J. Darden, B. Devany, E. Dorney, John Emmerson, Crauley Finney, Benjamin B. Foster, R.H. Gallason, Theodore S. Garnett Jr., H.A. Gilliams, America H. Glazebrook, John B. Glazebrook, L.W. Glazebrook, O.A. Glazebrook, Robert Glazebrook, Charles A. Green, David Hall Jr., C.B. Hayden, James G. Holladay, Benjamin E. Hope, J.H. Hope, Isaac R. Hunter, J.Beverly Hunter, James E. Jenkins, Thomas Johnson, William E. Jordan, H.H. Kelly, J.E. Kilby, W.M. Lain, Thomas Lawson, W.M. Levy, Mary A. Lewis, R.D. Lilly, Henry F. Lippold, J.F. McClellan, H.N. McTyerie, William Mahone, W.A. Massenburg, L.J.H. Meador, J.S. Meadows, John S. Millson, J.F.J. Mitchell, C.W. Murdaugh, W.W. Murray, J.O. Myrick, John S. Myrick, Thomas N. Myrick, R.E. Nash, A.W. Norfleet, David S. Parker, Nelson Parker, R.M. Parker, Richard G. Pegram, William Powell Jr., Robert S. Pretlow, E.C. Riddick, Nathaniel Riddick, Richard Riddick, W.L. Riddick, Washington Riddick, Willis Riddick, Robert R. Ritchie, Edward Robinson, Martha A. Scott, S. Shiffer, George W. Simpson, Joseph Sketer, R.N. Sledd, Arthur R. Smith, Edwin Smith, Sarah J. Smith, W.R. Smith, John W. Southall, William H. Stokers, W.C. Stuart, Robert H. Tatem, R.W. Walker, W.R. Whitehead, William B. Whitehead, Henry E. Whitfield, E. Williams, W.A. Williams, Thomas A. Wilson, John Wood Jr., T. Woodley, N.B. Worthington, William F. Wright, C.C. Yonge, and W.H. Young.
    - Accounts and receipts, 1834-1839 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Accounts and receipts, 1840-1842 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Accounts and receipts, 1843-1845 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Accounts and receipts, 1858-1859 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Accounts and receipts, 1860-1869 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Accounts and receipts, 1870-1877 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bank books, 1859-1877 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Bills of sale for slaves, 1840-1860 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Broadside, 1853 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Contract, 1850 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1843-1849 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1850-1855 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1856-1859 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1860-1867 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1868-1869 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1870-1875 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1876-1877 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, nd (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Estate accounts, 1852-1885 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Military records, 1843 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Oaths, 1852-1865 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Power of attorney, 1866 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Promissory notes, 1839-1875 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Stock, 1852-1859 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 2: Accounts books and ledgers, 1840-1904
    This subseries consists of estate accounts, account books, fee books, tax books, and overseer of the poor records of Nansemond County, Virginia. Of note are the tax account books for Nansemond, 1840-1844. These books contain listings of the taxes received by Kilby and signatures of members of the overseer of the poor committee. Also included is an account book of state taxes received on seals of notary public, 1853-1877; commissioner in fiduciaries account books, 1849-1882, and fee books, 1842-1844.
    The account books include estate accounts, 1843-1874, of Andrew Ballard, Julia A. Bunch, John S. Cutler, Mills C. Daughtrey, Peninah Eppes, Baswell Garrison, Charles Godwin, Marina Godwin, Sally Godwin, William H. Godwin, Joshua Harrell, Cadwallader Hawes, Josephine Hawes, Joseph Hill, William Holmes, Henry D. Jones, Harriet S. Kilby, William Turpin Kilby, Mourning Laurence, William Laycock, Joseph Meredith, John Mills, William Murphrey, Jesse Perry, Josiah Pinner, Archibald Riddick, Richard H. Riddick, Arthur Smith, and Sarah J. Smith. Many of the accounts include reference to slaves, including names and ages. These accounts include a listing of bills paid, monies divided among heirs, stock sold, supplies purchased, rent of land, hiring of slaves, interest earned, inventories, and an overall accounting of the settlement of the estates.
    Also included is a ledger of cash receipts for Kilby's law practice, 1846-1869; account books, 1855-1869, which contain a list of slaves, including names, birth and death dates, 1856-1861 (see accession 40340); and ledgers, 1846-1904.
    - Account book as administrator and guardian for Harrell, Pinner, Eppes, Hawes, Garrison, Smith, Meredith, Cutler, and Daughtrey families, 1843-1860 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Account book of Mrs. Sarah J. Smith, as guardian of Washington, Henning, and Robert Smith, 1852-1867 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Account book containing the estates of the Holmes, Murphrey, Ballard, Mills, Harrell, Godwin, Laycock, Laurence, Pinner, Hill, and Jones families, 1840-1852 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Account book of levies of the County Court and Overseers of the Poor, In and about Suffolk, Va., 1840 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Account book of levies of the County Court and Overseers of the Poor, In and about Suffolk, Va., 1841 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Account book of levies of the County Court and Overseers of the Poor, In and about Suffolk, Va., 1842 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Account book of levies of the County Court and Overseers of the Poor, In and about Suffolk, Va., 1843 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Account book of levies of the County Court and Overseers of the Poor, In and about Suffolk, Va., 1853-1877 (Box 7, Folder 8)